(Raj:)Also, what kind of name is Biff?
(Raj:)Sounds like when you pop open
a can of Pillsbury dough.
(Howard:)Biff.
(Howard:)Oh, that stuff is so good
wrapped around cocktail weenies.
(Leonard:)Guys...
(Sheldon:)Do you know that
the word "wiener"
(Sheldon:)comes from the German name
(Sheldon:)of the Austrian capital
Vienna, or "Wien"?
(Raj:)Do you know if you look
at Austria on a map
(Raj:)it actually looks like a wiener?
(Leonard:)Guys, what are
we doing?
W-We sent the girls away
(Leonard:)so we could focus.
(Sheldon:)I don't think it worked.
(lively dance music playing)
(Amy:)Maybe after this, you'll be
in the mood for some Manilow.
(Bernadette:)I think after this,
I'll be dead.
(Amy:)Look at us out,
(Amy:)while Penny's in
the room studying.
(Bernadette:)I'm proud of her.
(Bernadette:)This is a great opportunity.
(Bernadette:)It's nice to see her take it
seriously.
(Leonard:)It is.
(Amy:)But enough about Penny.
(Amy:)Let's talk about us.